Being active doesn’t have to mean
pumping iron five days a week.
But that’s cool if you want to!
For everyone else, the opportunity
to be active is all around.
In fact, you’re probably
more active than you think.
Yes, you!
With Manulife Vitality,
you could be earning
rewards by tracking simple,
everyday activities like regular
visits to the doctor and dentist,
taking the stairs
or hopping off the subway two stops
early to squeeze in a few more steps.
Fitting the little things
in is all it takes.
And since every little
move you make adds up,
why not keep score and
get rewarded for it?
Manulife Vitality empowers you to take
charge of your health, little by little.
And we’re with you
every step of the way.
Find out how to start tracking and
earning today at Manulife.ca/Vitality